learntopokemongo.com 2017-02-12

# Privacy Policy – Learn to Pokemon Go

Your privacy is very important to us. This privacy policy describes the information we gather, how we share that information and what we do to protect your information.

**Personal Information**

_QTX Media_  requires your e-mail address when you subscribe to our newsletters, when you sign up for sweepstakes, and when you take advantage of other services our website offers. To provide you with the best possible service, we also require some basic personal information when you sign up. Those items are marked with an asterisk (*). Furthermore, we ask for some optional information on our sign-up page and in periodic opt-in surveys. We use this basic and optional information, to further tailor our content to your interests. Upon request, we will provide you with the information that we maintain about you.

**Demographic Information  **

We may use aggregate data such as income, age and geography to further customize our content and enhance our services. We may share this information with advertisers and the media. Likewise, we may share this information with another company in the event that we merge, are acquired or participate in a joint venture with another company, or if we conclude that we are required by law to share it. All aggregate data will be shared without any personally identifiable information about our individual subscribers.

**Cookies  **

We and some of our partners may make use of cookies (small text files placed on your computer’s hard disk by our server). They are used to collect traffic information such as the number of visits to our site and pages visited. This information will be used to assess how visitors are using our services. This data will also allow us to manage the functionality of the site. You can disable cookies at any time if your browser permits.

**Web Site Usage Information**

We and our partners also may make use of pixel tags which also collect traffic information regarding the behaviour and usage patterns of users of our site.   Pixel tags allow us, or a third party who provides the pixel tag, to set, read, and modify cookies on, and to transfer other data to, the browser used to view the Web page or other document. Pixel tags may also be used to obtain information about the computer being used to view that Web page or other document, including the sites the users of that computer visit. The entity that provides the tag can view the IP address of the computer that the tag is sent to, the time it was sent, the user’s operating system and browser type, and similar information.  Our partners may use this information to display advertisements and other content that targeted to you.  We may also use other technologies that permit data gathering.

**Linked Sites**

Although  _QTX Media_  may provide links to third party sites, and advertisements from third parties, we are not responsible for the content that appears on those sites nor do we endorse these sites. Please review each site’s privacy policy to determine their use of information.

**Social Networking**

If you choose to access, visit and/or use any third-party social networking service(s) that may be integrated with the Service, we may receive personally identifiable information and other information about you and your computer, mobile and other device that you have made available to those services, including information about your contacts on those services. For example, some social networking services allow you to push content from our Service to your contacts or to pull information about your contacts so you can connect with them on or through our Service. Some social networking services also will facilitate your registration for our Service or enhance or personalize your experience on our Service. Your decision to use a social networking service in connection with our Service is voluntary. However, you should make sure you are comfortable with the information your third-party social networking services may make available to our Service by vising those services’ privacy policies and/or modifying your privacy settings directly with those services. We reserve the right to use, transfer, assign, share and provide access to all personally identifiable information and other information about you and your computer, mobile or other device that we receive through third-party social networking services in the same ways described in this Privacy Policy as all of your other information.

**Advertisers  **

To support our efforts we sell sponsorships of  _LearntoPokemonGo_  mailings and on the blog to advertisers who we think you’d like to know about. Collection, use, disclosure and security of information collected by advertisers are subject to the privacy policies of those advertisers.

**Agents  **

From time to time, we may use the services of third-party companies to help facilitate our business activities. These include affiliate or incentive program providers, customer service organizations, e-mail and postal mail brokers, and marketing service providers. These companies are subject to confidentiality agreements with us and are prohibited from using the information we provide for any reason except to perform the functions that we have outlined for them.

**Third Parties**

Company expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our Website, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices.

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose information (including personally identifiable information) on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond our control and outside the scope of this Privacy Policy.

Company is not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from the Website nor the information or content contained therein. It follows that the Company accepts no responsibility for events experienced by you if you visit a third party site by clicking through from the Website. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Website to another website, this Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. User browsing and interaction on any other website, including those that have a link on our Website, is subject to that other website’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

**Third Party Advertisements and Technologies:**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements when you visit the Website as is explained in detail in the Terms of Use. In the course of advertisements being served to you, a unique third-party cookie or other advertising technology may be placed on your browser. This advertising technology uses information derived from your visits to the Website to target advertising within this Website or on other websites. This information is used for many purposes, for example, it helps us try to ensure that you do not see the same advertisements over and over again. We also use this information to help select and display targeted advertisements that we believe may be of interest to you (sometimes called “online behavioral advertising” or “interest-based advertising” or “OBA”). We also use web beacons, provided by third-party advertising companies, to help manage and optimize our online advertising. Web beacons enable us to recognize a browser’s cookie when a browser visits this Website, to learn which banner ads bring users to our Website and to deliver more relevant advertising.

In addition, our advertisers or other third parties may use other third-party advertising technology to target advertising on the Website and other websites. We do not control the data collection and use practices of these other third parties. You should read the privacy notices of the websites you visit in order to determine what companies may be collecting information on those websites.

**Opt-out / Unsubscribe**

If we ever send you an email that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with an email address by which you may request to receive no future notices.

**Changes to Privacy Policy  **

_QTX Media_  may change this privacy policy. Any changes will be reflected on this privacy policy page. If you are concerned about how your information will be used, you should check back at this privacy policy page periodically.

**Children’s Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Company does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number or email address. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information to Company. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [info@LearntoPokemonGo.com](mailto:info@WomaninStrategy.com)

**Contact  **  
If you should have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us at Info@LearntoPokemonGo.com.
